JULIA: Chester's Mill is
a place like any other.
체스터스 밀은 평범한 마을이었다
At least, it used to be,
적어도 얼마 전까지는
until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
수수께끼의 돔이 덮히기 전까지는
by a mysterious dome.
(cows mooing)
(cow moans)
Invisible, indestructible,
투명하고, 부술 수도 없으며
-빠져나갈 수가 없다
-완전히 갇혔어
inescapable.
We're trapped.
우린 이 돔의 정체를
전혀 모르고 있다
We don't know where it
came from or why it's here,
but now that we're all trapped
under the dome together,
돔이 이 마을을 덮고 있는 상황에서
none of our secrets are safe.
더 이상 숨길 수 있는 비밀은 없다
(shouts, grunts)
안 돼...
Thanks again
for letting me crash here.
여기서 묵게 해주셔서
고마워요
My husband isn't here,
제 남편은 지금 여기 없지만
분명 돌아올 거에요, 바비
but he'll turn up.
You'll see, Barbie.
(shouts)
(gunshot)
That thing
is never going to go away.
저건 절대 없어지지 않을 거야!
(gunshots, bullets ricocheting)
Oh, no. No.
안 돼!
The pink stars
are falling in lines.
분홍색 별이 일렬로 떨어져요
(indistinct chatter)
Ride that dome!
Nice!
-돔 위에서도 잘타네!
-좋았어!
Whoa, Benny.
Dome ride was sick, bro.
야, 베니
돔 타는거 정말 멋졌어
PAUL (over video): It's not gonna be okay!
Yeah.
이건 평생 없어지지 않을 거야!
This thing is never gonna go
away, and we're all gonna die!
우린 다 죽을거라고!
(gunshots on phone)
Dude. You're watching
that video again?
이봐, 또 그 영상
보고 있는 거야?
I still can't believe it.
난 아직도 믿겨지지 않아
DAN: You weren't kidding
about that Barbie guy.
네 말대로 바비란 사람
정말 멋진거 같아
He took that cop's ass down.
경관 메다꽂는거 좀 봐
I wonder if Barbie's,
like, black ops.
첩보원이 아닌가 싶어
Oh, my God,
your phone still works?
-네 핸드폰은 아직 작동이 돼?
-좋겠다
So jealous.
Yeah, the camera and the apps.
카메라랑 일반 어플은 되는데
전화나 문자는 안 돼
Just... no texting or calls.
I miss texting.
문자가 그립다 정말
It's been, like, a day and a half.
Whatever.
-아직 하루 반 밖에 안 지났잖아
-그래도
Don't be judge-y.
너무 잔소리 하진 마
Dude. Show 'em.
얘네한테도 그거 보여줘 봐
It's never gonna go away,
이건 평생 없어지지 않을 거야!
-우린 다 죽을거라고!
-폴, 안 돼!
and we're all gonna die!
LINDA: Paul, don't!
(gunshots)
총알이 돔에 반사되듯 튕겨졌어
GIRL: The bullet just
bounced off the dome.
Did Paul mean to shoot Freddy?
폴이 일부러
프레디를 쏜 걸까?
I don't know.
모르겠어
He was acting pretty crazy.
그 사람은 제정신이
아닌 것 같았어
I wonder what they'll do
with him.
폴은 어떻게 되는 거지?
경찰을 살해한 경우
형벌은 엄청나
Cop killer's as bad as it gets.
Especially a cop
that kills another cop.
동료 경찰을 죽인 경우면
더욱이
You in a hurry or something?
바쁘신 일 있나요?
I want to get to
the police station
폴과 경관들이 도착하기 전에
경찰서에 가 보려고요
before they walk Randolph in.
What, you don't like my driving?
I...
운전하는 게
맘에 안 드세요?
아니요, 그런 건
아니지만...
Not that at all.
Just, uh...
조심하면서 운전하는 게
나쁠 건 없죠
Nothing wrong with using
a little caution.
I don't do caution.
지금 조심하지 않고 있거든요
(chuckles)
I noticed.
알고 있었어요
당신 정말...
You're a real...
run-towards-the-fire
kind of girl, aren't you?
무모하고 용감한
분인 것 같네요
I'm a journalist.
전 기자잖아요
I've got to find out
all I can about this dome
전 돔에 대한 정보를
최대한 많이 알아낼 거에요
so me, you and everyone
in this town
가능한 빨리 당신과 저
우리 모두가 빠져나가게요
can get out as soon as possible.
I've got a husband out there
I'd kind of like to see again.
밖에 있는 제 남편을
어서 다시 보고 싶어요
(brakes squeak)
MAN:
There he is.
저깄다
에스키벨 경관님
Deputy Esquivel.
That was a pretty daring
코긴드 목사님을 구해주신 건
정말 용감했어요
thing you did, pulling Reverend
Coggins out of the fire. MAN: Killer!
Just doing my job.
So, what, with the entire
전 제 일을 한 건 뿐이에요
지금 소방관들 전부와
경관 절반이 돔 밖에 있고
fire department
and half the police force
stuck outside the dome and
now two officers dead...
-2명의 경관이 더 죽었는데...
-용건이 뭐죠?
What's your question?
Can you handle this alone
until we find
여기서 빠져나갈 때까지
혼자 일 처리 가능하겠어요?
a way to get out?
우린 괜찮을겁니다,
셤웨이 부인
We'll be fine, Mrs. Shumway.
서로서로 주의한다면요
Long as we all
look out for each other.
-살인자 놈!
-나쁜 놈!
Murderer!
Killer!
Let's get him!
Hey!
Any more of that,
and I'll haul your ass in!
계속 이러시면
당신들도 체포하겠어요!
PAUL:
Hey, it was the dome
that did it to Freddy!
내가 아니라
돔이 그런거야!
It's gonna kill more
before it's done!
-돔이 이걸로 끝내진 않을 걸?
-어서 안으로 데려가게
Take him inside.
I can control this.
여긴 내가 제어해보겠네
Oh, so you're in charge now?
이젠 당신이 책임자라고요?
Friends!
여러분
I'm asking you all
to let the law do its job.
이제부턴 경찰이 알아서
처리할 겁니다
몇 시간 전 경찰이
무고한 사람이 죽였잖아!
- The law did its job already--
killed an innocent man. - No, no, no.
그건 비극적인 사고였습니다
That was a tragic accident.
As the town's
only remaining councilman,
마을에 남은 유일한 의원으로서
I will not countenance any kind
전 공정치 못한 재판은
용납 안 할 겁니다
of frontier justice.
이제 다들 집에 돌아가서
Now, you go home,
손을 모아
clasp hands
프레디의 영혼을 위해
기도해주십시요
and pray for Freddy Denton's
poor soul.
돌아가세요
Go on.
이걸 유튜브에 올려야 하는데 말야
BEN: Too bad we can't upload
that video to YouTube.
(chuckles)
GIRL: Excuse me.
저기 미안한데,
혹시 MP3 충전하는 데가 어디야?
Where can a girl charge up in this town?
Um...
I have a generator at my...
발전기가 있어, 우리...
Your house?
너네 집에?
BEN:
We saw you
화재 사고 때
널 봤었는데
at the fire.
여긴 어쩌다 오게 됬어?
Uh, how'd you end up here?
I just followed some kids.
애들 따라왔어
Heard 'em talking
about a bonfire.
캠프파이어 한단 얘길
들었거든
No, I meant, how...
I knew what you meant.
-아니, 내 말은...
-아, 무슨 뜻인지 알겠어
I was on my way someplace and...
다른 곳에 가던 중이었는데...
시기가 안 좋은 바람에
같이 갇히게 된 거야
Wrong place
at the wrong time, I guess.
난 빌붙는 걸 싫어하긴 하는데
I'm not usually a mooch,
but without my music,
음악을 못 들으니까
좆나 이렇게 할 수밖에 없네
I can get a little,
you know, super bitchy.
네 충전기 좀
빌려도 될까?
Can I refuel at your place?
Sure. There's no one
home except me...
-그래, 어차피 집에 나밖에...
-그래
Cool.
사실 묵을 곳도 필요했거든
I actually need
a place to crash, too.
If that's okay, I mean.
네가 거부만 안 한다면...
Oh...
너랑 같이 있는
두 여자 분을 봤는데
Well, I mean, I saw
you with two ladies.
I thought you were with them.
-일행 아니야?
-잘 모르는 사람들이야
Never seen 'em before.
So...
그러면...
cool to crash?
묵어도 돼?
PAUL:
I'm sorry.
미안해
프레디는 내 파트너이자
친구이기도 했어
Freddy, he was my partner,
and he was my friend,
but he wouldn't be dead
if it weren't for this dome.
이 돔만 아니었어도
걘 죽지 않았을 거야
You're gonna have to tell Rusty.
러스티에게 그렇게 말해 줘
He'll understand.
러스티도 이해할 거야
Like hell he will!
He's Freddy's brother!
이해하긴 개뿔!
둘이 형제잖아!
대체 우리가 뭘 잘못했다고...
What did we do to deserve this?
(wheezing)
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
Paul?
폴?
(grunting)
I warned you, Linda.
내가 경고했지, 린다
난 어떤 일이 벌어질지
다 경고했어
I warned you what would happen.
This is all
a misunderstanding, Paul.
잘못 생각하고 있는 거야, 폴
No, it's not.
그렇지 않아
It's the dome.
돔이 그런 거야
It's making everyone crazy,
and it's going to kill us all.
돔이 모두를 미치게 만들고 있어
우릴 다 죽일 거야
If the town doesn't
kill me first.
마을이 먼저 날
죽이게 두진 않을 거야
Paul.
폴
Paul!
폴!
Under The Dome
Season 1 Episode 3
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Manhunt
수색
(refrigerator humming)
(sniffs)
Where were you yesterday,
Junior?
어제 어디 있었니, 주니어?
Nowhere.
아무데도요
(refrigerator door opens)
주민들이 불을 끄기 위해
Whole town pulls together
to put out a fire.
But you?
모두 협력할 때
넌 뭘 했니?
어디에도 없더구나
"Nowhere" to be found.
-아빠
-조용히 있어
Dad...
Shut your mouth.
Mmm.
사람들이 내게 기대하고 있어
People are looking to me.
지도자로서 말이야
To lead.
To stand up, like a man does.
사람들 앞에
나서라고 말이야
It reflects poorly
아들이 자꾸 무단이탈을 하면
when my son is AWOL.
그 일에 도움이 안 돼
이 상황은, 또 다른 기회야
This situation,
it's an opportunity.
All your life, I've provided you
with advantages.
난 항상 네 인생에
도움을 줘 왔어
Opening doors.
많은 일을 할 수 있게 했지
Like with the football team.
네 풋볼 팀 일도 그렇고
-그건 제가 원하지도...
-요점은
Dad, I never wanted to play...
Point is
네 인생은 기회들로 가득 차 있단 거야
you only get so many chances
in life.
그걸 놓치지 말라고
Do not squander them.
네 얼굴은 왜 그러니?
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
No, what...
-아무것도요
-아니, 이게...
Who did this to your face?
누가 그런 거니?
그 남자요
This guy.
이름이 바비였던 것 같아요
His name's Barbie, I think.
He's totally insane.
완전히 미친 사람이에요
네 엄마가 세상을 떠난지
9년이 지났어
Nine years it's been
since your mother died.
엄마 치마 폭에
숨는 듯한 행동은 여전하구나
And still it's like
you're hiding behind her skirt.
좀 강해지거라, 주니어
Best toughen up now, Junior.
날 실망시키지 마
Don't you let me down.
(door shuts)
WYBS 방송입니다
PHIL (over radio):
Your dial's set to WYBS,
체스터밀의
정말 단 하나뿐인
the only-- and I literal
mean the only--
뉴스 방송입니다
source of news here
in Chester's Mill.
인사말이 있겠습니다
Couple of shout-outs:
first, to everyone
어제 불을 끄기 위해
양동이를 잡으신 분들께 감사합니다
who grabbed a bucket yesterday
and joined
the volunteer brigade.
협동심을 유지하는
좋은 일이었죠
Way to stay
civic-minded, people.
그리고 코긴스 목사님을 구해주신
린다 에스키벨 경관님께
And big ups
to the lovely Linda Esquivel
(click, keys jangling)
for her daring rescue of Reverend Coggins.
매우 감사드립니다
(door creaks)
(door shuts)
I made you some eggs.
계란 요리야
단백질이 필요할 것 같아서
Figured you could use
some protein. (chuckles)
나도 알겠어
I get it.
너 화났지, 그렇지만...
You're angry, but...
이 돔이라는 것 때문에
지금 너가 이상한 거야
it's the dome
that's making you act like this.
돔 때문이 아니야
Nothing's making me act
like this.
네가 나를 여기에
이틀 동안 가둬놨잖아
It's you locking me
down here for two days.
Everything is gonna go back
to the way it was before.
모든 게 다 예전처럼
돌아가게 될 거야
두고 봐, 앤지
You'll see, Ange.
Soon as we get out
from under this thing.
우리가 여기서
벗어나게 되면 말이야
지하로 가 본 사람 있어?
Has anyone tried going under it?
People took shovels and tried digging...
No.
-땅을 파 본 사람들은 많은데...
-아니
내 말은...
지하 말이야
I mean... way under it.
Like through the cement factory
tunnels.
시멘트 회사 터널 같은
곳으로 말이야
They closed those off...
전에 폐쇄되었잖아
after the flood
홍수가 나서
그 안에 있던 애들이 죽었을 때
when those kids
died down there.
It's dangerous.
-위험해
-그래도 우리는 종종 거기에 가봤잖아
You and I still went down there
all the time.
Walked through the tunnels
터널을 지나서
웨스트레이크 마을 경계선도
넘어가 보곤 했었지
till we came across
the town line into Westlake,
차를 얻어타서
다시 돌아왔었고
hitchhiked back.
네가 맞을 지도 몰라
Maybe you're right.
Maybe...
아마도...
네가 출구를 찾게 되면
많은 게 바뀔 거야
things would be different
if you could find a way out.
어쩌면 우린 다시...
Maybe we could...
시작하게 될지도
start over.
I'll be back later.
나중에 돌아 올게
정신차리고 일어나게, 목사
Rise and shine, Reverend.
(coughing)
뭔 생각이었나?
The hell were you thinking?
증거를 찾아서 없애라고 했지
집을 불태우라고 했나?
I told you to find
the evidence and destroy it,
not torch a dead man's house.
난 그럴 려 했던 거야
I did what you told me.
프로판 가스 계산서에다가
불을 붙였지
Found the bills of sales
of propane, set 'em on fire--
all the evidence destroyed,
just like you asked.
자네가 부탁한 대로
모든 증거가 사라졌잖나
Listen up, Lester.
잘 듣게, 레스터
Now the only files left
that can implicate us
이제 우리를 프로판과
연루시킬 만한 단서는...
in this drug business...
이 안에 밖에 없어
are right here.
그러니 이 단서들을
지키기 위해
So we have to trust each other
on the security of those.
우리는 서로를 믿어야 돼
영안실로 가서
프레디 시신이나 처리하게
Scoot on back to the mortuary
and take care
of Freddy Denton's corpse.
하필이면 그동안 선례도 없고
초자연적인 일이 발생한 날에
JULIA:
So, what are the odds
that you, just passing through,
happen to be here
on the day that
an unprecedented,
당신이 이 마을에 있던건
정말 우연의 일치인가요?
possibly supernatural
event occurred?
God, I swear,
you ask more questions
당신 정말 누구보다도
질문이 많군요
than anybody I've ever met.
자꾸 대답을 피하려 들지 마시고요
Well, you know you're
pretty good at evading them.
그리고 전 기자거든요
And asking questions is my job.
당신 자꾸 기자라는 핑계로
본인 얘기는 안 하려 하는군요
That's just your way of keeping
people from asking you anything.
All right.
좋아요
당신이 질문 해봐요
Your turn.
How does someone
당신같이 야망있는 기자가
왜 체스터스 밀에 사는 거죠?
as ambitious as you
end up here in Chester's Mill?
제 남편이 여기서 자랐어요
My husband grew up here.
그리고...
And, uh...
상황이 돌아가다 보니
circumstances shifted,
and it just made sense for us,
여기에 살게 되더군요
you know, to... come here
and start over.
다시 잘 시작하기 위해서
이곳에 왔었어요
That's our DJ, Phil.
DJ 필이에요
-만나보실래요?
-아니요
You want to meet him?
Uh, no.
I'll let you guys
get to... work.
일하시는 데...
방해하기 싫어서요
I'm gonna get a bite
to eat at the diner.
전 식당에 좀 갈 게요
린다, 어딨나?
BIG JIM:
Linda? Where are you?
짐! 짐!
Jim! Jim!
짐! 여기에요!
Jim, I'm down here!
저기에 열쇠요
The keys.
-폴 랜돌프는 어딨나?
-도망갔어요
Where's Paul Randolph?
He escaped.
린다, 자네는 이 경찰서를 관리할
준비가 되어 있어야...
Linda? I'd hoped you were
ready for the responsibility
of running this department...
Jim, with all due respect,
I don't need a lecture.
죄송하지만,
지금은 강의하려 하지 마세요
숨 좀 돌리게, 지금
미친 범법자가 탈주했다고
Take a pause.
We have a disturbed fugitive
on the loose.
As councilman,
시 의원으로서
it is my job to organize
a search party.
수색조를 꾸리는 것은
내 일일세
그럼 가서 하세요
Then go do it.
전 더는 다른 사람이
다치게 내버려 두지 않아요
But I'm not gonna wait
for someone else to get hurt.
-젠장, 폴이 소총을 가져갔어
-어디로 갈 건가?
Damn it, Paul. He took a rifle.
Where you going?
블랙 리지 숲이요
폴 사냥을 나가던 곳이에요
Black Ridge Woods.
He likes to hunt there.
Listen to me. It's too risky.
-내 말듣게, 위험하다구!
-짐!
당신이 사람들 제어하는 걸
좋아하는 건 알지만
Jim, I know you like
to control things,
나한테는 안 돼요
but you do not control me.
걱정할 거 없어
연구 중인 정부의 과학자들이
Why worry? I bet they got
government scientists
tapping on that thing,
trying to figure out
우리와 대화하는 방법을
고안해내고 있을 거야
how to talk with us in here.
여기로 베이컨 넣어주는 방법이나
고안해 내면 좋겠군
Maybe they'll figure out
how to get us more bacon.
Bacon's the least
of our worries, Roger.
지금 베이컨 걱정 할 때가
아니에요, 로저
Any sign of your daughter?
딸 소식은 있나요?
지난 밤부터 감감무소식이에요
Not since last night.
앨리스가 찾아다니고 있어요
Alice is out looking for her.
I can't help but think
that it's just another one
노리가 또 발작을 일으켜서
길바닥에 쓰러져 있는 건 아닌지
걱정되네요
of those seizures
and Norrie's laying unconscious
on the side of a road somewhere.
아마 괜찮을 거에요
Oh, now, I'm sure she's fine.
저기 죄송합니다만,
Excuse me, sir. You...
혹시라도 제 딸 본 적 없나요?
wouldn't, by any chance,
have seen my daughter?
딸이라고요?
그게 가능한가요?
Your daughter? How's that work?
저랑 제 애인은
동성애자거든요
My partner and I are
a same-sex couple with a child.
여긴 21세기입니다
Welcome to the 21st century.
What are you doing here
in Chester's Mill anyway?
체스터스 밀에서는
왜 오셨던 겁니까?
노리를 어디 데려다 주는 길에
갇혔어요
We got stuck here
on our way to drop Norrie,
our daughter--
제 딸...
원래 남편과 낳았던 딸을...
our legitimate daughter--
사립 학교로 데려다 주는 거에요
off to a nearby private school.
Oh. The girl's
reformatory, you mean.
소년원 말하시는 거군요?
거기 가면 그 애가 나중에
게이라도 낳아 줄 것 같아서요?
Think they can pray
the gay out of her?
이쪽으로 와 보세요
Why don't you come
with me, honey?
커피 한 잔 드릴게요
Let's get you a cup of coffee.
당국은 아직 돔의 구성요소나
근원을 파악 못하고 있습니다
Authorities outside still
don't know the composition
or the origin of the dome.
답이 나올 때까지는
말을 하지 않을 계획 같군요
Presumably they'll keep at it
until they get some answers.
(click, song plays)
이런 식의 공생 관계
마음에 드네요
I like this symbiotic thing
we got going on, man.
정상적인 사회를 유지하려면
정보를 많이 줘야 해요
Key to a civilized society
is a well-informed public.
옥내 화장실도 꼭 필요합니다만
Oh, that and indoor plumbing.
Oh. I forgot
about indoor plumbing.
아, 그걸 있고 있었네요
화장실은 꼭
계속 작동이 되길
Fingers crossed that holds out.
(chuckles)
Where's Junior off to
in such a hurry?
주니어는 저렇게 바쁘게
어딜 가는 거죠?
모르겠네요
I don't know.
의원 아들놈인데
It's the councilman's
kid, though.
마을의 특종 기사를
많이 빼낼 수 있는 놈이잖아요
If anyone's got
the inside scoop, it's him.
Junior!
주니어!
어디 가는 거니?
Where you headed?
그냥... 하이킹이요
Just... going for a hike.
헬멧은 왜 가져 가니?
What's with the helmet?
I don't have to answer your questions.
제가 거기에 대답할
필요는 없죠
여긴 자유국가잖아요
It's a free country.
Thank you.
고마워요
앉아도 되나요?
Do you mind?
그럼요
당신 마음대로죠
Hey. It's your joint.
하긴, 이 식당 전부가
제 거긴 하니까요
All mine, it seems.
점심 타임에 일하던
앤지라는 애가 있는데
Had a girl, Angie, working
the lunch counter,
but I haven't seen
her since Dome Day.
'돔 데이' 이후에는
안 보이네요
So, how's it been
staying over at Julia's?
줄리아 집에서
자는 건 편하세요?
Nice and comfy?
(bell jingles)
작은 마을에선
소문이 빨리 퍼지죠
Small town, kiddo.
원래보다 더 작아졌잖아요
It's only gonna get smaller.
BIG JIM: All right,
listen up, people.
다들 주목해 주세요
말씀드릴 게 있습니다
I got an announcement to make.
전 경관 폴 랜돌프가
서에서 탈출했습니다
Former Deputy Paul Randolph
has escaped police custody.
혹시 모르니,
사건이 해결 되기 전까지는
Just as a precaution,
I'm gonna ask you all to stay
in your homes until
this situation is resolved.
집에 가 있으시길 바랍니다
현재 수색조를 꾸리는 중이니
I'm also putting together
a search party, and I'm asking
가능하신 남성 분들은
동참하시길 바랍니다
if any able-bodied men
are keen to join up.
난 껴 주게, 빅 짐
Right here, Big Jim.
나도 들어가겠네
Count me in, too.
좋습니다
All right.
로저, 올리
고맙네
Roger, Ollie, thank you much.
(quietly): Now, listen, boys, he's already
assaulted two other people,
이 자는 이미 2명의 사람을
공격했어
그리고 케스퍼 백화점에서
and he's stolen a mass
of provisions
대량의 식량을 훔쳐갔네
from Casper's Department Store.
지금은 도망 중이야
Now, he's on the run,
하지만 이 마을엔
숨을 데가 많잖아
but there's only so many
places he can hide.
He took a rifle from
the police station,
폴은 경찰서에서
총도 훔쳤어
so bring your firearms.
그러니 자네들도
화기를 가져오게
I don't believe we've been, uh,
우린 정식으로 인사를
한 적이 없는 것 같군요
formally introduced.
I'm, uh, Jim Rennie.
전 짐 레니입니다
People around here
call me Big Jim.
마을 주민들은 저를
빅 집이라고 부르죠
-전 바비입니다
-바비요
Barbie.
Well, that's kind of
a funny name
당신의 직업 동료들이 붙혀준
웃긴 별명같은 거군요
for a fellow
with your particular expertise.
어제 폴의 총을 뺏는 걸
봤습니다
I saw you take that gun
off Randolph yesterday.
혹시 현상금 사냥꾼이신가요?
What are you, a bounty hunter
or something? (chuckles)
농담으로 해 본 소립니다
Ah, just kidding, of course.
폴은 그렇게
쉬운 상대가 아니거든요
This Paul Randolph's no fish
in a barrel. He was a...
이라크에서 2번이나 근무를
했던 해병대놈입니다
a Marine, served
two tours in Iraq.
Oh.
은성 훈장도
받았던 놈이죠
Yeah. Won a Silvertar.
Perfect.
그렇군요
그래서...
So...
Barbie,
바비
당신도 수색에
참여할 건가요?
you in or out?
This is Phil Bushey
with an update
현재 진행 중인
수색 작전 소식과 함께 돌아온
concerning the ongoing
manhunt in town.
필 부시입니다
Former Deputy Paul Randolph's
squad car
전 경관 폴 랜돌프의 차량이
블랙 리지 숲에서
has been spotted off the road
at Black Ridge Woo.
발견되었습니다
체스터스 밀 주민들은
사태가 해결될 때까지
All Chester's Millers
are under an advisory
집에서 나오지 말기를
권고드리는 바입니다
to stay home until
the situation is resolved.
차를 버리고 갔군
Looks like he abandoned it.
Fellas, I got something
over here.
팰라스, 여기 뭐가 있어
Come on. This way.
어서, 이쪽이야
잠깐만요
Hey. Hold on.
폴은 군사 훈련을
받은 사람이라고 했죠?
This guy's got
military training, right?
저런 분명한 흔적은
분명히 거짓일 거에요
That's a dummy trail-- he'd
never do anything that obvious.
Look at this.
이걸 봐 봐요
These branches here,
they're all broken.
이쪽 나뭇가지들이
모두 꺽여 있어요
Right there.
여기요
Our man came right
through here.
이쪽으로 간 게 틀림없어요
See, I knew you'd be useful.
난 당신이 유용할 줄 알았어
(wood cracking, creaking)
(water dripping)
♪
(beep)
(music playing in background)
Do you always eat standing up?
넌 항상 일어나서 음식 먹냐?
동물들도 일어나서 먹잖아
Animals eat standing up.
Good point, Joe.
그래,알겠다 조
These are really good.
They're, like, better
이거 정말 맛있다
우리 엄마들이
홀 푸드 가게에서 사오는
than those Amy's Breakfast
Scramble Wraps
스크램블 샌드위치보다
훨씬 맛있어
my moms buy at Whole Foods.
엄마'들'?
Your moms?
Yeah, my moms, my pops,
you know, like they say.
응, 엄마들, 아빠들
그냥 다 그러잖아
너네 부모님은
어디 계셔?
Where are your parents?
밖에 계셔,
아빠는 대형 트럭을 운전하셔서
Outside.
My dad drives a rig, so...
he's gone a lot, and...
지금 멀리 계시고
my mom was in Westlake,
the next town over, when...
엄마는 옆 마을
웨스트레이크에 가셨어
그 일이 벌어졌을 때...
너네는?
you know.
What about yours?
난 아빠를 보러 가는
길이었는데... 알잖아
I was on my way to visit
my dad and... you know.
He's a musician.
아빠는 음악을 하셔
대형 트럭을 모는 것도
나름 멋진 일인 것 같네
Budriving a rig's
pretty cool, too.
우리 둘 다 비교적
자유로운 상황이네
Guess we're both
unsupervised, huh?
BEN: Hey, Joe-Joe!
(knock at door)
이봐, 조!
이 아름다운 두 여성 분께서
These two lovely ladies
were hoping
네가 직접 만든 전기를 좀
쓰고 싶다시는데?
to take advantage
of your sweet,
sweet homemade electricity.
My family
doesn't have a gennie.
우리 집엔 발전기가 없거든
Mine, neither. And the
music they play on WYBS
우리 집도, 그리고 WYBS 방송은
정신병자같아서 듣기가 싫어
is, like, totally schizo.
Did you invite anyone else?
너 또 여기에 초대한 사람 있어?
Uh, I might have mentioned
the generator to a few people.
몇 사람들에게 발전기에 대해
얘기하긴 했는데
다 집에 있으라는
마을 경보는 어쩌구?
What about the whole
advisories-to-stay-inside thing?
여긴 아포칼립스 상황이라구!
마을 경보는 먹히지 않아
Dude, it's the apocalypse.
Advisories don't apply.
(chuckles)
Nice.
좋잖아
Please tell me you hit that.
솔직히 너도 좋다고 말해
(scoffs)
Uncool, bro.
Leave a brother hanging.
쿨하지가 못해
그냥 가버리냐
BIG JIM: Just like Butch
and Sundance, huh?
꼭 '버치 앤 샌더스' 같군
BARBIE: Are we the good
guys or the bad guys?
우리 역할은 착한 놈인가요
나쁜 놈인가요?
당신 군인이었죠?
You're military, aren't you?
어제 폴을 제압할 때나
아까 흔적 추적하는 모습을 보니까
The way you disarmed Randolph
and the...
the whole dummy trail business?
그냥 쫄병이었습니다
No, I was just a grunt.
그래도 전지에 가 본적은 있죠?
But you were over there,
weren't you?
You ever been to war?
전쟁에 참가해보셨습니까?
No.
아니요
그럴 영광이 없었습니다
Never had the privilege.
(groaning)
PAUL:
Hey!
이봐!
다음 번엔 더 위를 겨냥해주겠어!
Next time, I'll aim higher!
I'm warning you guys,
you better leave me alone!
네가 경고했지
날 내버려두라고!
I don't want to hurt
anyone else!
더 이상 누군가를
다치게 하기 싫어!
(Roger groaning)
Ollie, take Roger back to town
올리, 로저를 마을로 데려 가
저 미친놈이
다시 나타나기 전에
before that lunatic
takes another pop at us.
You and me,
we're finishing this thing.
우리 둘은 이 일을 같이 끝냅시다
정확한 목적이 뭐죠?
What is your
objective here, huh?
Is it to bring him in, or are we
trying to take him out?
체포하려는 겁니까?
사살하려는 겁니까?
I don't see it makes
a difference
당신같은 사람에게는
그 둘의 차이가 모호하지 않나?
to a guy like you, does it?
What, to a guy like me?
'저 같은 사람'이요?
해가 지고 있으니
빨리 갑시다
We're losing the light.
Let's move it.
JUNIOR.
I found a way out.
나가는 길을 찾았어
(grunts)
Don't!
안 돼!
(Junior gasps)
날 미행한 걸
후회할 텐데
You shouldn't have followed me.
여긴 왜 온 거죠?
Why did you come down here?
네가 출구를 찾았으면 해서
내려와 본 거야
I was just hoping
you'd find a way out.
실망시켜서 죄송하네요
Sorry to let you down.
I hate this thing.
난 이게 너무 싫어
(deep whirring)
I... hate you.
난 네가 싫다고...
(yelling)
(yelling continues)
(yells)
(panting)
주니어...
Junior...
are you okay?
괜찮니?
아니, 이 터널은...
매우 위험해요
No. These...
these tunnels are dangerous.
They're like a maze.
미로같다고요
이 어두운 데서
출구를 어찌 찾죠?
How can you even find
your way out of the dark?
And they're even more dangerous
with this thing cutting into it.
더군다나 돔이 터널을 잘라서
더 위험하다고요
무너지면 어쩌죠?
What if it collapses on us?
여기서 죽은 사람들도 있다고요
People die in here.
난 굴에 갇힌 광부에 관한
I did a story once
on coal miners,
guys trapped underground.
기사를 써 본적이 있어
You see the way
the flame flickers?
불꽃이 깜빡거리는
방향이 보이지?
You know which way
the air flows,
이걸 보면 공기가 흐르는
방향을 알 수 있어
you follow it home.
그걸 따라가면 돼
Let's go home.
어서 집에 가자
(squeals, snorts)
♪
BEN: Dude, you're not
gonna believe this.
이봐, 이게 믿겨져?
The guys got
얘네가 루프로 되어있는
심슨 극장판 필름을 가져왔어
The Simpsons Movie
going on a loop.
They totally saw
the dome coming.
여기선 돔이 오는 걸 다 보던데?
얘네들 언제 나간대?
When can I ask people to leave?
Scarecrow Joe.
허수아비 조!
Nice house party, bro.
하우스 파티 재밌는데?
Carter. Used to go out
with your sister.
난 카터야
네 누나 전 남친이었어
Well, stayed in
more than we went out,
걔랑 사귈 때보다
여기 더 오래 있는 것 같다
if you know what I mean.
(chuckles)
초대해줘서 고마워, 꼬마친구
Thanks for inviting us
in, little man.
We'll just make
ourselves at home.
편히 놀다 갈게
생각해 봐
Think about it.
넌 지금 네 집이 생긴 거야
You have a house to yourself.
You could become
the most popular guy in town.
이 마을에서 가장 유명한
애가 될 수도 있다구
Maybe even get
저 중에서 네 여친이
생길지도 모르고
a girlfriend out of it.
쟤가 널 좋아하는 것 같아
She digs you.
I've got an instinct
about these things.
난 이런 거에 대한
통찰력이 있다구
Just don't tell her about
that funky seizure you had.
네가 발작했단 얘긴 하지마
Don't want her
to think you're a spaz.
널 바보라고 생각하게
하지 말라구
그건 정말
바보같은 행동이니까
Total spaz move.
저거 좀 작동시켜보러 가자
Let's work on that, dude.
Can you remember
which way we came?
우리가 왔었던 길
기억 나니?
I don't have a lot
of matches left.
성냥이 몇 개 안 남았어
어차피 의미도 없어요
Who cares?
굴에 갇혀죽나, 돔에 갇혀죽나
We're trapped down here,
we're trapped out there.
차이가 없잖아요
What's the difference?
(sighs)
I just wanted
to do something good today.
전 오늘 그냥 좋은 일을
하려던 것 뿐이에요
나서서 좋은 일을 하는 사람
A man stands up.
A man doesn't screw up.
실수 안 하는 사람이
되고 싶었어요
We all screw up.
모든 사람은 다 실수를 해
We make bad choices.
나쁜 선택을 하곤 하지
제 아빠께 그 말 좀 해주세요
Tell that to my father.
내가 어쩌다 이 마을로
오게 됐었는지 알아?
You want to know how I ended up
in Chester's Mill?
I was covering the
mayor's race in Chicago.
난 시카고에서 시장 선거를
보도하는 일을 했었단다
The guy in the lead
당시 지지율 1위 후보자가
극조직정치를 했었어
was a real machine politician.
I really wanted
to take him down.
그래서 나는 그를
떨어뜨리고 싶었어
About a week
before the election,
선거 1주일 전
내 정보원 중 하나가
one of my sources
sent me some documents
그 후보자의 뇌물 혐의가 담긴
서류를 보내왔어
that showed bribery.
I thought the leaked
docs might be forged,
나는 그 서류의 조작가능성을 의심했지만,
but I went ahead with
the story anyway.
그 내용을 그대로 보도를 했어
And it blew up in my face.
일이 잘못되었지
내가 거짓말을 했다는 게
밝혀지게 되었고
The truth about
my little lie surfaced,
그 후보자는 당선되었지만
the guy got reelected,
and I was fired
난 해고당하고
불명예를 얻었지
and disgraced.
그래서 내가 지금 여기 있는 거야
And now I'm here.
So I know from
screw-ups.
실수한다는 게 어떤건진
내가 잘 알지
한 가지만 더 말하자면
Tell you one thing, though.
I will never make
that mistake again.
나는 더 이상
같은 실수를 하진 않을 거야
계속 가 보자
We just keep moving forward.
CARTER:
Who needs some juice?
주스 먹을 사람 있어?
Whoa, hold up, freshie.
어이, 잠깐!
그만큼에 5달러야
Five bucks for five minutes.
Should I do something
about this?
저거 가서 말해봐야 되지 않아?
함부로 말했다간
네 얼굴 피카소그림 꼴 날 걸?
Yeah, and get your face
Picasso-ed by a guy
who's got 25 pounds on you?
He doesn't run our electricity.
저 자식이 전기를
돌리는 것도 아니잖아
Did you ever take
American History?
너 미국 역사 수업
들어본 적 있니?
Uh, yeah.
어, 그런데
그러면 셔먼 트러스트 금지법에
대해서도 들어봤겠네?
So you know about
the Sherman Antitrust Act?
글쎄, 아마도?
I don't know. Maybe.
못 들어본 것 같네
Maybe not. 'Cause if you had,
들어봤다면 지금 이게
불법이라는 걸 알 테니까
you'd know that what
you're doing is illegal.
Monopolies are illegal.
모노폴리(독점)는 불법이야
Monopoly's not illegal.
모노폴리가 불법이라니?
We have the board game
at my house. (chuckles)
우리 집에 모노폴리
보드게임판도 있는데
Well, then maybe you should go
back to your house.
그럼 당장 너네 집으로 돌아가
가서 혼자 놀라구
Play by yourself.
(Carter chuckles)
혼자보다는 너랑
같이 놀아보고 싶은데?
I think I'd rather play
with you, red.
Why don't we
take this upstairs?
이거 위층으로 데려가 볼까?
여기서 나가
I think you should leave.
Oh, I am leaving, little man.
나갈 거야, 꼬마 친구야
I'm going up
to your sister's room.
네 누나 앤지네 방에 갈 거야
I don't think she'd mind.
전에도 갔었기 때문에
앤지도 싫어하지 않을 걸?
I've been there before.
No. I want you
to leave my house.
아니, 내 집에서
아예 나가라고
저리 꺼져, 당장
Move. Now.
Or this gets ugly fast.
안그럼 사태가 험악해 질거야
(people groaning)
발전기가 터졌어
GIRL:
The generator blew.
This ain't even close to over,
Scarecrow.
아직 안 끝났어,
허수아비새끼야
JUNIOR: How many matches
do we have left?
성냥 몇 개 남았어요?
One.
한 개
이 일엔 다 이유가 있어요
There's a reason for all this:
돔이랑...
the dome,
all those people who died.
죽은 사람들 말이에요
바비라는 작자가 마을에 오면서
이런 일이 생겼어요
This all happened when
that Barbie guy showed up.
문제에 대한 답을 찾지 못했다고
Sometimes,
when we don't understand
the answer to a thing,
we look for someone to blame.
다른 사람 탓으로 돌리는 건 참 쉽지
그러니 이해가 되는 군요
Oh, I understand.
난데없이 절 쳤던 것도
이해가 되요
I understand he attacked
me out of the blue.
이거 보이죠?
See this?
You know how I got that?
어쩌다 이랬는지 아세요?
Good old Barbie.
친절한 바비 씨가
그런 거에요
People think he's this hero,
사람들은 바비를
영웅으로 알고 있지만 실은...
but he's a psychopath.
싸이코패스 놈이에요
Barbie just attacked you
for no reason?
바비가 이유없이
널 공격했다고?
That's right.
맞아요
You don't know this guy.
당신은 바비를 잘 몰라요
I mean, what's he
really doing here?
제말은, 그 놈 대체
여기서 뭘 하는 거죠?
전에도 이 마을에
온 적이 있을까요?
Has he been here before?
이런 질문에 대한
대답을 받아봐야 돼요
He has to answer some questions.
이제 어쩌죠?
What do we do now?
(Julia exhales sharply)
(door creaks)
가자
Come on.
집까지 태워다 줄게
I'll give you a ride home.
BARBIE: I think we ought
to call it a day here
이쯤에서 그만하고
내일 다시해야 할 것 같아요
and get a fresh start tomorrow.
Why's that? So we can give
Randolph a chance to get away?
함부로 그랬다가 랜돌프에게
도망칠 시간 벌어주려고?
Come on, man.
We're sealed in here.
여긴 다 막혔잖아요
어디로 도망을 가겠어요?
Where the hell's he gonna go?
I told you we're
finishing this.
끝내고 가기로 했잖나
Why is that?
왜요?
So you can show the town
what a big man Big Jim is?
빅 짐이 얼마나 대단한 사람인지
보여주려고요?
You ever play football, Barbie?
풋볼 해본 적 있나, 바비?
No. I was never much
of a team sports kind of guy.
아니요, 전 운동 팀에
잘 끼는 부류가 아니었어요
(chuckles)
나는 코너백을 맡았었지
I played cornerback.
A lot of smaller guys play
스피드와 민첩성을 필요로해서
'cause it requires
speed and agility.
보통 체구가 작은 사람이
맡는 포지션이지
우리 풋볼 팀에는
주에서 유명한
Back in school, we had
this all-state wideout,
정말 허풍쟁이 놈이...
한 놈 있었는데
a real, uh... a real
showboater, you know?
그 놈이 날 "빅 짐"이라고 불렀지
He called me "Big Jim," uh,
but as a joke, you know?
농담으로 나를
비꼬는데 쓰는 말이었어
Laughing at me.
그리고 어느날
싸움이 있었는데
And one day we, um...
we had to scrimmage,
and he was taunting me,
you know?
그놈이 또 나를 조롱해댔어
"와 봐, 빅 짐..."
"Come on, Big Jim," you know?
"어디 한 번 덤벼보라구..."
이렇게 말야
"You can't touch me, Big Jim,"
you know?
그래서...
So...
I put the mother of all hits
on this punk.
난 그 양아치새끼를
개패듯이 패기 시작했지
I mean, helmet first,
went in low,
그 놈 면상부터 시작해서...
아래쪽으로 가서
completely shattered his pelvis.
골반까지 부숴놔줬지
Guess what.
그랬더니 말야
Big Jim wasn't a joke no more.
'빅 짐'이란 말은
다신 놀리는 용도로 쓰이지 않았어
What does that tell you?
자네 생각은 어떤가?
I don't know.
글쎄요
당신과 같은 팀이 아니었단게
다행인 것 같네요
Tells me that being on your team
could be hazardous to my health.
가끔씩은 본보기를
보여줘야 할 때도 있는 걸세
Sometimes an example needs
to be made, you know?
존경을 얻기 위해서
Command respect.
An eye for an eye.
눈에는 눈, 이에는 이지
(twigs snap)
짐?
Jim?
(gun cocks)
저 놈을 죽일 거야
I'll kill him...
just like he was gonna kill me.
저 자식이 날 죽이려던 것 처럼
-아무도 당신이 죽길 원하지 않아
-방금 저 자가 말했잖아
Nobody wants to kill anybody here.
He said it himself.
An eye for an eye, right?
눈에는 눈이라고?
본보기를 보여준다고?
Make an example out of me.
무기 내려놔
Drop your weapon now.
무기 당장 내려 놓으라고
I said drop your weapon now...
(gunshot)
(body thuds)
(door opens)
(sighs)
BIG JIM:
Evening to you, Lester.
좋은 저녁일세, 레스터
I'm sorry to say
we brought you another customer.
정말 미안하네만
시신이 또 있네
COGGINS: I'm not finished
with Deputy Denton yet.
프레디 경관 작업도
아직 끝내지 못했어
Patching a wound takes time.
상처를 처리하는 과정이
오래 걸리거든
Paul Randolph
needs your help, too.
폴 랜돌프도
자네 도움이 필요하게 됐군
주님께서 우리 능력 이상의
일거리를 주는 것 같구만
The Lord never gives us
more than we can handle, Rev.
(door opens)
아무에게도 말 안했지?
You clean?
당연하지, 짐
Absolutely, Jim.
Any red you see in my eyes,
that's overwork, nothing else.
내 눈이 충혈된 건
과로때문이지, 딴 게 아니야
Let's keep it that way.
계속 그렇게 잘 하게
Hey, would you mind
waiting at the car?
잠깐 차에서 기다려 줄 수 있나?
I need to talk to Linda.
린다에게 할 말이 있어서
Yeah. Sure.
네, 그럼요
미안하네
I'm sorry.
자네의 헌신을 의심한 거랑
For questioning your dedication
or if, in any way,
I insinuated that...
자네가 듀크의 자리를
이어받을 능력이 없다고
you weren't capable
of filling Duke's shoes.
생각했던 것들을 말이야
He'd be proud of you, you know.
듀크는 자네를 자랑스러워 할 거야
Fact, I bet he's
up there right now,
지금도 저 위에서
쇠고기 구이랑
감자요리를 먹으면서
eating roast beef
and mashed potatoes
with the Big Guy,
looking down on you and smiling.
미소지으며 내려다보고
있을 걸세
We're gonna do big things,
you and I.
자네와 나는 큰 일을 해 낼거야
우선 자네 아래에 둘
경관들을 임명해야 하네
First, we got to get you
some deputies.
새로운 경찰 서장도 필요할 거고
There's a new sheriff in town.
새 서장 이름은 린다 에스키벨이라네
And her name is Linda Esquivel.
Um, so...
오늘 일어난 일들은...
I was wondering
if maybe we could...
우리 둘 사이
비밀로 남겨두는 게 어때요?
keep what happened today
between us.
어차피 비밀은
누구에게나 있는 거잖아, 주니어
You know, we all
have secrets, Junior.
(chuckles)
제임스라고 불러주세요
You can call me James.
전 항상 주니어라고
불리는 게 싫었어요
I never did like
being called Junior anyways.
I'm guessing
you're a scotch guy.
자네 스코틀랜드 사람 맞지?
(chuckles)
You don't miss much, do you?
놓치는 게 없으시군요
Straight up, of course.
당연하지
(car doors open)
그럼 다음에 또 만나죠
Uh, maybe we should do this
another time.
(door opens)
여긴 작은 마을이라구
It's a small town, son.
(door shuts)
모두 같은 팀을 응원한다네
And we all support the team.
What was that about?
저게 무슨 소리죠?
Long story.
말하자면 길어요
폴 랜돌프
프레디 덴턴
♪
듀크 퍼킨스
(sighs)
대체 무슨 문제에
휘말려 있는 거냐?
What kind of trouble
you been getting into?
No trouble.
문제가 있는 게 아니에요
I went down into
the cement works
시멘트 공장 터널에 들어가서
and tried to find a way out.
출구를 찾으려고 해 봤어요
(grunts)
Failed, huh?
실패했겠지?
네
Yeah.
The dome goes straight through.
돔이 아래까지 연결되어 있었어요
당연히 그랬겠지
Well, of course it does.
You didn't think
it'd be that easy, did you?
그렇게 쉬울 거라
생각한 건 아니지?
바비란 놈하곤
뭘 하셨던 거죠?
What were you doing
with that Barbie guy?
That's none of your business.
-그건 네 일이 아니다
-제 일로 만들 거에요
I'll make it my business.
내가 허락하지 않는 이상
그럴 수는 없다
Not unless I tell you to.
Don't you worry
your head over Barbie.
쓸데없이 바비에 대한
생각하진 말거라
어른들이 알아서 하게 냅둬
Let the grown-ups do their job.
(glass clinks on bar)
Drink your milk, now, Junior.
네 우유 마시거라, 주니어
-뭐 하는 거야?
-나도 잘은 모르겠어
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Um, maybe I can fix it.
고칠 수 있을지도 몰라
정말?
Really?
스타워즈의 '죽음의 별'처럼
터져버렸는데?
That thing blew up
like the Death Star.
Yeah, but the Empire
rebuilt the Death Star
그 후에 제국이 다시
죽음의 별을 건설했지
in The Return of the Jedi.
'제다이의 귀환'에서
It was almost
fully operational.
거의 완벽히 작동했었잖아
난 너같은 괴짜가 좋아
I like nerds.
(knocking)
CAROLYN: Norrie?
노리?
(door opens)
Oh, God.
이런 젠장
노리, 너 여깄...
Norrie, are you here...?
(sighs)
케럴린, 날 어떻게 찾은 거야?
Carolyn, how did you find me?
아까 여기서 큰 소리가 들리던데
Something goes boom
in a small town,
엄마가 알 만도 하지
parents tend to know.
Let's go.
가자
Wh-Who is this lady?
이 분은 누구셔?
She's one of my moms.
우리 엄마들 중 한 분이야
One of your...
Okay, I guess there's just
-엄마들 중...?
-이건 내가 너에게
some things I didn't
want you to know about me.
설명해 주고 싶지 않은 내용이야
그래도 암튼...
But, hey...
thanks for almost
getting beat up for me.
아까 날 지켜줬던 건 정말 고마웠어
That was...
그건 정말...
kind of chivalrous.
남자답고 매너 있는 행동이었어
(low humming)
-맙소사, 노리?
-무슨 일이에요?
Oh, my God. Norrie?
What happened?
-분홍색 별이 떨어져요...
-노리
JOE and NORRIE: The pink stars are falling.
CAROLYN: Norrie!
-분홍색 별이 일렬로 떨어져요...
-노리
The pink stars are falling in lines.
Norrie.
-분홍색 별이 일렬로 떨어져요...
JOE and NORRIE: The pink
stars are falling in lines.
Norrie!
The pink stars are falling.
-노리
-분홍색 별이 떨어져요...
Norrie!
The pink stars are falling.
-노리
-분홍색 별이 떨어져요...
CAROLYN: Get help!
The pink stars
-도와줘! 어서!
-분홍색 별이 떨어져요...
are falling.
Go!
분홍색 별이...
The pink stars are...
(lock sliding, door clicking)
(door creaking)
Angie?
앤지?
Did you make it under?
지하로 가 봤어?
Uh-uh. Uh...
출구는 없었어
There's no way out.
내가 확실히 확인해 봤어
I made sure of it.
What happened to your hands?
손은 왜 그래?
(chuckles)
내가 돔을 쳐 봤어
I beat on that thing.
손전등이 나갈 때까지 서서
계속 쳐 봤어, 앤지
Stood up
and beat on it until the lights
went out, Angie.
(chuckles)
'Cause I love you.
널 사랑하기 때문에
♪
생각해 보니 전에
당신이 절 용기있다 했던 건
So, that comment that you made
about me running into the fire
was aggravatingly hypocritical.
약이오를 정도로
위선적인 말이었군요
(chuckles)
오늘 당신이
빅 짐과 한 일에 비하면
No, especially
considering the adventure
어제 제가 했던 일은
아무것도 아니었죠
you went on today with Big Jim.
Yeah, but there's a difference
between me and you.
그렇지만 당신과 전
차이점이 있어요
How so?
그게 뭐죠?
전 사건 해결만 나면
항상 바로 자리를 떴죠
I take off after the fire's out.
수습하는데 도움주지 않고요,
물론...
I mean, at least,
when there's somewhere
to take off to.
갈 데가 있었긴 했지만요
You bruised your knuckles.
손 관절에 멍이 들으셨네요
Yeah.
네
I bruised my knuckles.
멍이 좀 들었죠
당신 정말로 우연히
이 마을을 지나가던 중이었나요?
And you really
were just passing through
Chester's Mill?
No connection
to anyone here in town?
이 마을 사람들과는
어떤 연관도 없고요?
Nope.
그런 거 없습니다
잘 자요, 줄리아
Good night, Julia.
(door opens and closes)
(water running)
체스터스 밀
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
한글자막 by 뒷북()